<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Welcome to the Sale</title>
    <link>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Welcome to the Sale</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://welcometothe.sale/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Product Manager @Heetch</title>
      <link>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/heetch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/heetch/</guid>
      <description>Status Permanent contract 🚧 January 2018 - &amp;hellip;
Started from the bottom&amp;hellip; Heetch is one of Uber&amp;rsquo;s French competitor. Basically the app offers a more social and fun experience than what Uber can offer with a very premium, high end service.
I joined in January 2018 as a Junior Ride Product Manager with Walid Ellec as a mentor. During those first months I shipped my first user facing features and started getting ahead of what being a PM meant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-founder @Rapsodie</title>
      <link>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/rapsodie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/rapsodie/</guid>
      <description>Intro I&amp;rsquo;d say that project mixes two of the most important things I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered in my whole life: rap music and education. For those of you who already read a bit about my previous Deepdives project this is basically the personal spinoff I made from it. For the others, let&amp;rsquo;s meet below.
Status Side project 🚧 November 2017 - &amp;hellip;
Inside out What feels more natural than trying to replicate something we already made in the past for others?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-founder @Deepdives</title>
      <link>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/deepdives/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/deepdives/</guid>
      <description>Intro This is part 2 (and last) of my entrepreneurial adventure with the amazing [Charlotte Moreau](). The first part is our attempt at launching Nabu&amp;rsquo;s sign language translation wristband.
Status Personal Project ☠️ February 2017 - September 2017
After Class This project&amp;rsquo;s objective was pretty simple: how could one keep learning about new subjects without being feeling old-school-taught or bored?
We started with a first iteration as a messenger bot called Charade (try it out 🇫🇷).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Co-founder @Nabu</title>
      <link>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/nabu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/nabu/</guid>
      <description>Intro This article is the first part of a 2 article-long adventure with the amazing [Charlotte Moreau](). I will write a dedicated article about the human adventure itself but let&amp;rsquo;s focus on the product and achievements for now.
Status Personal project ☠️ August 2016 - February 2017
Go Bears! When I left Paris for UC Berkeley (with a bricked computed) I never knew the &amp;ldquo;Jedi wristband&amp;rdquo; project I was bringing with me would follow such an amazing path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mechanical Engineering intern @Withings</title>
      <link>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/withings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/withings/</guid>
      <description>Status Internship ✅ February 2016 - August 2016
French Touch Withings might be one of France&amp;rsquo;s finest companies. Founded by serial entrepreneur Eric Carreel (who also founded Inventel, Scuplteo, Zoov&amp;hellip;) their products have always pioneered in the health connected devices field. Their historic connected scale has enlightened the way for many more successful products such as watches, sleep monitors etc&amp;hellip; During my internship I had the opportunity to work on the Steel HR connected smart watch along with Manon Navellou.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mechanical Engineering intern @Dreem</title>
      <link>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/dreem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welcometothe.sale/projects/dreem/</guid>
      <description>Status Internship ✅ September 2015 - February 2016
Dream Dreem Rythm&amp;rsquo;s @Dreem sleep headband aims at helping people sleep better by increase deep sleep duration through noise stimulation. In XXX 2018 they released their third iteration of the headband. I had the opportunity to work on the beta version that was about to be release at the time.
During my 6 months internship I worked closely with the head of Mechanical Engineering on many key subjects such as</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>