<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>welcomethe.sale</title>
    <link>http://welcometothe.sale/</link>
    <description>Recent content on welcomethe.sale</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://welcometothe.sale/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>🚧 Heetch - Product Manager (Driver Growth)</title>
      <link>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/heetch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/heetch/</guid>
      <description>w budowie&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚧 Airworkie - Slack&#39;s future /remote command</title>
      <link>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/airworkie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/airworkie/</guid>
      <description>w budowie&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🚧 Rapsodie - Bringing rap music and education together</title>
      <link>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/rapsodie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/rapsodie/</guid>
      <description>w budowie&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>✔️ Nextdoor - Product Manager (Community)</title>
      <link>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/nextdoor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/nextdoor/</guid>
      <description>w budowie&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>✔️ Schoolab - Design Thiking Consultant</title>
      <link>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/schoolab/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/schoolab/</guid>
      <description>card Design thinking consultant working with corporates @Schoolab to help them imagine, design, prototype the tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s business solutions.
expand What&amp;rsquo;s great about these freelance missions is that they allow me to meet and interact with very different types of people and jobs in a wide spectrum of industries. I had the chance to imagine VISA&amp;rsquo;s next generation of credit cards, or L&amp;rsquo;Oréal&amp;rsquo;s tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s offices and work environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>❌ deepdives.io - co founder</title>
      <link>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/deepdives/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/deepdives/</guid>
      <description>card 7 months to launch a web-app to help people learn about tomorrow key subjects.
Started as a messenger bot called Charade. Pivoted to aim at companies&amp;rsquo; employees to train them, with the help of research chairs, on high-impact subjects such as AI, circular economy, IoT …
expand We started this project because of the recommandation problem we face. Everybody is always flooded into content (articles, videos, musics&amp;hellip;) that follow the same stupid principle: you liked it once, you&amp;rsquo;ll want more and more and more and more of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>❌ Nabu - co founder</title>
      <link>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/nabu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/nabu/</guid>
      <description>card 4 months startup working on a sign language translation wristband.
Started the project when in UC Berkeley. Back in Paris the customer interviews showed us this was not the right solution to this problem.
expand This project was originally borned as the jedi wristband where we wanted to interact with our environment using only gestures. We soon realised that if we wanted to build some solid ventures the gadget could not be the main value proposition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>✔️ Withings - ME intern Steel HR</title>
      <link>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/withings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/withings/</guid>
      <description>card 6 months mechanical engineering internship @Withings to design Steel HR smart watch case and wristband.
expand During my internship @Withings&amp;hellip;Nokia Health I had the chance to launch my own product!! Incredible experience where I was the one designing both wristbands for both models and the big watch case. I had the chance to travel to China and set up the assembly line with local partners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>✔️ Dreem - ME Intern Headband</title>
      <link>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/dreem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://welcometothe.sale/projects/dreem/</guid>
      <description>card 6 months mechanical engineering internship @Dreem. Responsible for all in-house prototyping and part of technical solution design for industrialization.
expand Rythm is a french neuroscience startup which aim is to help people sleep better. Employee #32. I was in charge of all prototyping and assisting the head of mechanical engineering in the product design before industrialization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://welcometothe.sale/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://welcometothe.sale/about/</guid>
      <description>WTF 👋 My name is Rashad but you already knew that, didn&amp;rsquo;t you? I&amp;rsquo;m in the biggest pivot of my professional life from launching my own startup to joining a new incredible team. I&amp;rsquo;m very social, team-focused and goal-oriented. I believe I&amp;rsquo;m demanding towards myself and others. I want to make a real impact and dive 100% into my (our) next adventure.
On the other side, I&amp;rsquo;m also a positive and optimistic person who loves spending good moments with my loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>