<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Welcome to the Sale</title>
    <link>https://welcometothe.sale/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Welcome to the Sale</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://welcometothe.sale/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>🧪 Your Product Report</title>
      <link>https://welcometothe.sale/articles/product-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welcometothe.sale/articles/product-report/</guid>
      <description>I am trying a brand new format regarding access to a product expertise. I want to offer you a free product report and analysis along with some feedbacks on whatever you&amp;rsquo;re working on.
The Process I&amp;rsquo;ll test out the product you send me and provide you with a report on how well it&amp;rsquo;s performing product-wise. Among others, I&amp;rsquo;ll look at the overall quality of the product, how well it&amp;rsquo;s solving the issue it&amp;rsquo;s supposed to solve, how seamless the user experience is, and provide you with some improvement suggestions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>🌠 A Product Vision</title>
      <link>https://welcometothe.sale/articles/product-vision/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welcometothe.sale/articles/product-vision/</guid>
      <description>There are a lot of people talking about product out there. Like a lot. How do you know I&amp;rsquo;m the one you need for your amazing secret project? Well let me introduce you to my product vision.
What the f*** is &amp;ldquo;product&amp;rdquo; anyway? Basically anything you&amp;rsquo;re serving your users is product-related. The obvious part is made of UX and UI design of course but not only, your tech stack and the way you use your data (if any) change make go from a meh product to a great product!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>👶 Product Management Starter Pack</title>
      <link>https://welcometothe.sale/articles/pm-starter-pack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://welcometothe.sale/articles/pm-starter-pack/</guid>
      <description>(disclaimer) This blog post comes from an email I&amp;rsquo;ve sent to a couple of my friends who were looking into product management. After many people shared it I though it could be useful to random people who wanted to get to know what PM was about. It would need to be updated and it&amp;rsquo;s in French. I&amp;rsquo;ll update that asap I promise 🤞
Ce que j&amp;rsquo;ai fait perso ce n&amp;rsquo;est absolument pas une vérité absolue, c&amp;rsquo;est essayer de me créer une culture produit sur tout ce qui passe sous mon nez.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>